virtapay.com 2012-11-12

# VirtaPay

Privacy Policy 

Email Newsletter 

If you subscribe to any of our email newsletters, we will use your email address to send the newsletter to you. Our newsletter is "Double Opt-in". You can unsubscribe ("opt-out") at any time, in which case your email address will be permanently removed from our database. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter, simply follow the unsubscribe instructions included at the end of every newsletter. 

The email addresses of people who have joined our email newsletter are never sold, rented, leased, traded, swapped, exchanged, bartered, etc. We don't like to receive junk mail, and know you don't either. 

Website Visitors 

Like most website operators, VirtaPay collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each browser request. Our purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how our visitors use our website. From time to time, VirtaPay may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of our website. 

VirtaPay also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. VirtaPay does not use such information to identify our visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below. 

Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information 

Certain visitors to our website choose to interact in ways that require VirtaPay to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that VirtaPay gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, visitors who join our email list provide an email address. In each case, VirtaPay collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction. VirtaPay does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. Visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

Aggregated Statistics 

VirtaPay may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to our website. However, VirtaPay does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. 

Children's Privacy 

You must be thirteen years or older to access this website. If you are under thirteen years of age, you are not permitted to access this website for any reason. Due to the age restrictions for use of this website, no information obtained by this website, falls within the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), or similar child protection laws of other countries, and is not monitored as doing so. 

Protection of Personally-Identifying Information 

VirtaPay discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of our employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf or to provide services available at our website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using our website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. VirtaPay will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to our employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations, as described above, VirtaPay discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when we believe in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of VirtaPay, third parties, or the public at large. VirtaPay takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

Cookies 

A cookie is a small bit of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. 

For VirtaPay to function properly, you must have cookies enabled when you log in. We also use cookies to help us identify and track visitors, their usage of our website, and their website access preferences. Cookies may also be used to store transient preferences that don't require longer term storage. 

In addition, when using the VirtaPay website, third parties may place cookies on, and read cookies from your browser, or use "web beacons" to collect information, in the course of serving advertisements on our website. 

VirtaPay visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using our website, with the drawback that most features of our website will not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

Third Parties 

We use website code from several third-party services within the code of our web pages. If you have questions or concerns about the privacy policies or privacy practices of any of these or other third-party services which you may notice on our website, please contact those websites directly. 

A few of the third-party services used on our website include: 

  * [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/privacy.html) \- We use this service for web traffic analysis. The analytic reports help us to understand which areas of our website receive the most traffic. This helps us to improve the overall speed, functionality and user experience of the website. 
  * [AddToAny](http://www.addtoany.com/privacy) \- We use this service to allow our users to more easily share with their social networks. 

We may add more services or remove any of those listed in the future. As we make changes we will try to keep this list updated. 

Privacy Policy Changes 

Although most changes are likely to be minor, we may change our Privacy Policy from time to time, and in our sole discretion. We encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to our Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
